(Penny:)Oh, hi. What's going on?
(Leonard:)We're up on the roof
bouncing laser beams off the moon.
(Penny:)I'm sorry, what?
It's cool. We've got a two-meter
parabolic reflector and everything.
-I thought you might wanna see it.
-That makes no sense.
(Man:)How can you bounce stuff off the moon?
There's no gravity.
Oh, Leonard, this is Zack. Zack, Leonard.
(Leonard:)-Hey.
-Sorry, I didn't know you were busy.
(Leonard:)-Maybe another time.
-Yeah. Maybe.
-Hey, I wanna see this laser thing.
-Oh, what about the party?
(Zack:)It's a surprise party,
doesn't matter when we get there.
(Howard:)Right.
(Leonard:)Okay, well, yeah, come on up.
LEONARD:
So how'd you guys meet?
ZACK: My company designs the menus
for The Cheesecake Factory.
LEONARD:
Your company?
ZACK:
My dad, but me and my sister are VPs.
LEONARD:
So menus.